[
    {
        "id": "001",
        "question": "What does SASS stand for?",
        "answers": [
            "Super Amazing Sleek Styles",
            "Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets",
            "Strangely Arranged Syntax Structure",
            "Sweet and Sour Scallops"
        ],

        "correct_answer": "Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets"
    },

    {
        "id": "002",
        "question": "SASS files are saved with what extension?",
        "answers": [
            ".sass",
            ".css",
            ".scss",
            ".sassy"
        ],

        "correct_answer":".scss"
    },

    {
        "id": "003",
        "question": "SASS is a preprocessor language compiled by what language?",
        "answers": [
            "CSS",
            "HTML",
            "React",
            "Angular"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"CSS"
    },

    {
        "id": "004",
        "question": "What is the correct way to store a variable in SASS?",
        "answers": [
            "$primary-background-color: #ce6699",
            "primary-background-color = #ce6699",
            "primary-background-color = $#ce6699",
            "variable = primary-background-color = $#ce6699"
        ],

        "correct_answer":  "$primary-background-color: #ce6699"
    },

    {
        "id": "005",
        "question": "Which of the following is used to apply similar styles to a selected field from another field?",
        "answers": [
            "@media",
            "@extends",
            "@import",
            "@apply-styles"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"@extends"
    },

    {
        "id": "006",
        "question": "What symbol is used when nesting selectors in SASS?",
        "answers": [
            "&",
            "$",
            "@",
            "%"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"&"
    },

    {
        "id": "007",
        "question": "What does Jon yell when he succssfully debugs code?",
        "answers": [
            "When is lunch?",
            "Of course I knew the answer",
            "Kiss my SASS - I knew it",
            "It Worked!"
        ],

        "correct_answer": "It Worked!"
    },

    {
        "id": "008",
        "question": "What selector is used when selecting a class?",
        "answers": [
            ".",
            "#",
            "$",
            "*"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"."
    },

    {
        "id": "009",
        "question": "What selector is used when selecting a ID?",
        "answers": [
            ".",
            "#",
            "$",
            "*"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"#"
    },

    {
        "id": "010",
        "question": "What method is used to condense/simplify your styling code?",
        "answers": [
            "@extends",
            "@import",
            "@variables",
            "@mixin"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"@mixin"
    },

    {
        "id": "011",
        "question": "What method is used to import a SASS file into a HTML file?",
        "answers": [
            "<stylesheet rel='stylesheet.scss' type='stylesheet'>",
            "<stylesheet href='stylesheet.scss' type='stylesheet'>",
            "<stylesheet href='stylesheet.scss'rel='stylesheet'>",
            "none of the above"
        ],

        "correct_answer":  "none of the above"
    },

    {
        "id": "012",
        "question": "What does BEM stand for?",
        "answers": [
            "Block Element Modifier",
            "Block Element Model",
            "Big Eel Meal",
            "Branch Element Model"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"Block Element Modifer"
    },

    {
        "id": "013",
        "question": "What is Jon's record for demoing one slide?",
        "answers": [
            "1.5 hours",
            "2 hours",
            "30 minutes",
            "1 hour"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"1 hour"
    },

    {
        "id": "014",
        "question": "What display method is used to arrange items in a container?",
        "answers": [
            "display: arrange",
            "display: row",
            "display: flex",
            "display: shuffle"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"display: flex"
    },

    {
        "id": "015",
        "question": "What method is used to reverse the direction of a flexed container?",
        "answers": [
            "row/column reverse",
            "reverse-flex",
            "flip-items",
            "justify-content: space-between"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"row/column reverse"
    },

    {
        "id": "016",
        "question": "What rule aligns items along the center of the main axis?",
        "answers": [
            "justify-items: center",
            "justify-content: center",
            "align-items: center",
            "align-content: center"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"justify-content: center"
    },

    {
        "id": "017",
        "question": "What is Lauren's favourite phrase?",
        "answers": [
            "sup-guys?",
            "howdy students!",
            "do you to take up the lab?",
            "it is imperative that you remember this"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"sub-guys"
    },

    {
        "id": "018",
        "question": "How many real-life backgrounds does Angus have?",
        "answers": [
            "five",
            "three",
            "two",
            "six"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"five"
    },


    {
        "id": "019",
        "question": "What animal is known to be the loudest one on earth?",
        "answers": [
            "sperm whale",
            "howler monkey",
            "male lion",
            "african elephant"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"five"
    },

    {
        "id": "020",
        "question": "What are media queries?",
        "answers": [
            "something the browser uses for accepting media",
            "a method to conditionally add rulesets",
            "a way to improve media related items",
            "a method to access media APIs"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"a method to conditionally add rulesets"
    },

    {
        "id": "021",
        "question": "What is Jessica's favourite game?",
        "answers": [
            "tic-tac-toe",
            "catan",
            "zoom whack-a-mole with Angus",
            "mantarry"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"zoom whack-a-mole with Angus"
    },

    {
        "id": "022",
        "question": "What array method is used to remove the last item?",
        "answers": [
            ".remove",
            ".pop",
            ".push",
            ".pull"
        ],

        "correct_answer":".pop"
    },

    {
        "id": "023",
        "question": "What was the first computer virus named?",
        "answers": [
            "Elk Cloner",
            "Max Uppercut",
            "Blue Steel",
            "Baby Softcheeks"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"Elk Cloner"
    },

    {
        "id": "024",
        "question": "Which property is used to color text?",
        "answers": [
            "background-color",
            "font-style-color",
            "font-color",
            "color"
        ],

        "correct_answer":"color"
    },

    {
        "id": "025",
        "question": "Where does the link for your style sheet belong?",
        "answers": [
            "HTML <header></header>",
            "HTML <body></body>",
            "HTML <footer></footer>",
            "HTML <head></head>"
        ],

        "correct_answer": "HTML <head></head>"
    },

    {
        "id": "026",
        "question": "Who is the father of the computer?",
        "answers": [
            "Alan Turing",
            "Charles Babbage",
            "John Galt",
            "Satoshi Nakamoto"
        ],

        "correct_answer": "Charles Babbage"
    },

    {
        "id": "027",
        "question": "a:hover is an example of what?",
        "answers": [
            "pseudo-class",
            "selectors",
            "link attributes",
            "SASS extensions"
        ],

        "correct_answer": "pseudo-class"
    },

    {
        "id": "028",
        "question": "Which selector will select all <p></p> elements?",
        "answers": [
            "#p{}",
            ".p{}",
            "<p>{}",
            "p{}"
        ],

        "correct_answer": "p{}"
    },

    {
        "id": "029",
        "question": "What does CSS stand for?",
        "answers": [
            "Crazy Style Site",
            "Cascading Style Sheets",
            "Cranky Style Sheets",
            "Crypto Style Site"
        ],

        "correct_answer": "Cascading Style Sheet"
    },

    {
        "id": "030",
        "question": "How long did it take Brendan Eich to create JavaScript?",
        "answers": [
            "10 hours",
            "10 weeks",
            "10 days",
            "10 minutes"
        ],

        "correct_answer": "10 days"
    }
]